Andrea Fazio

JUNIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior fullstack developer

The Level Group | September 2022 - now

I am handling the management and development of e-commerce in the fashion and luxury industry using Salesforce Commerce Cloud.

I am inclined to develop both frontend and backend with various programming languages such as: Javascript, React, Redux, JQuery, Laravel and Node.

These languages have been studied over time through training hours that company gives me and from my curiosity to experiment with new methods.

Trainee Caposettore

Leroy Merlin| September 2019 - September 2020

Management of department resources (ex: schedules and implementations of ranges/trade operations) to hit the goal; advance rank planning business strategies (analysis of new products, reuse of materials, optimal stock management and increased visibility).

Co-construction of store strategy in collaboration with other locations; reshaping organization and sales strategy as a result of Covid-19.

EDUCATION

Junior Web Developer

Boolean Careers | January 2021 - July 2021

In this experience, I made challenging projects inspired by famous websites and web apps, such as: Netflix, Whatsapp Web, Spotify Web, and so-many more.

The final project represents a simulation of developing a site similar to Airbnb being part of a team chosen by PM, mainly I was in charge of the backend part and building the advanced search with interactive map insertion with TomTom API calls. Find the BoolB&b project here.

Bachelor's Degree in Industrial Engineering

Università di Catanial October 2013 - December 2018

Topics subject to further study: electrical engineering; mechanics applied to machines; construction science; thermodynamics; heat transfer; machines and energy systems.

Writing of the thesis entitled "The automotive transmission and its evolutions" For consultation you can find it at this <u>link</u>



OVERVIEW

In addition to being a developer, I am also an engineer. Since high school there has been a strong passion for computer science and technology with a clear goal in mind: to maximize the potential of the tools at hand and improve processes.

SOFT SKILLS

- Leadership
- Cooperative
- Goal orientation
- Analyst and decision marking
- Adaptive spirit
- Communicative

HARD SKILS























My project on github /fazioandreaf

CONTATTI



+39 3403093979



fazioandrea.f@gmail.com



fazioandrea-f



AndreaFazio